
 [
    {
      "question": " A system of beliefs based on teh teachings of confucius",
      "choice1": "confucianism",
      "choice2": "Daoism",
      "choice3": "Legalism",
      "choice4": "Hinduism",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "A Chinese philosophy concerned with obtaining long life and living in harmony with nature",
      "choice1": "confucianism",
      "choice2": "Daoism",
      "choice3": "Legalism",
      "choice4": "Hinduism",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "A Chinese philosophy that stressed the importance of laws.",
      "choice1": "confucianism",
      "choice2": "Daoism",
      "choice3": "Legalism",
      "choice4": "Hinduism",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "A group of people who are at a similar culture, economic or educational level",
      "choice1": "ancestor",
      "choice2": "Family",
      "choice3": "cult",
      "choice4": "social class ",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The responsibility children have to respect, obey and care for their parents.",
      "choice1": "filial piety",
      "choice2": "legalism",
      "choice3": "Hereditary",
      "choice4": "Daoism ",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "A central idea of Confucianism",
      "choice1": "Vedas",
      "choice2": "Duty",
      "choice3": "meditate",
      "choice4": "an eye for an eye",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Confucius believed that people should do their duty and they should place the needs of __________ and _________ above his or her own needs",
      "choice1": "Kings and queens",
      "choice2": "kings and princes",
      "choice3": "communities and family",
      "choice4": "rulers and slaves ",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Who did Chinese farmers serve during wartime?",
      "choice1": "soldiers",
      "choice2": "Kings",
      "choice3": "Queens",
      "choice4": "Confucius ",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Confucianism influenced Chinese _____________ and ______________.",
      "choice1": "Rulers and slaves",
      "choice2": "society and government.",
      "choice3": "Men and women",
      "choice4": "All of the above",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "To Confucius, the right way to live was similar to the ____________.",
      "choice1": "buddhists",
      "choice2": "Hindu",
      "choice3": "Golden Rule",
      "choice4": "Ten commandments",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Hanfeizi introduced legalism to ancient China and he believed humans were naturally __________.",
      "choice1": "evil ",
      "choice2": "smart",
      "choice3": "kind",
      "choice4": "crazy",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Some Chinese merchants became wealthy, but they were not ______________ members of society.",
      "choice1": "helpful ",
      "choice2": "holy",
      "choice3": "respected ",
      "choice4": "American",
      "answer": 3
    }  
  ]
